Guide to the Lively Arts at Stanford Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lively Arts at Stanford records.
1972-1984
SC0509
Lively Arts at Stanford
Stanford University. Stanford Events.
17 Linear feet (34 boxes)
The records include correspondence, contracts, memoranda, photographs, clippings, brochures, and programs pertaining to performers in the Lively Arts series, 1972-1984.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received by the Stanford University Archives via administrative transfer from Stanford Events in 1996.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Lively Arts at Stanford is a yearly performance series featuring dance, music, and theater.
Description of the Collection
The records include correspondence, contracts, memoranda, photographs, clippings, brochures, and programs pertaining to performers in the Lively Arts series, 1972-1984.
Arrangement note
The records are arranged chronologically and then alphabetically within each chronological grouping. The records from 1972 through 1978 were kept together in one grouping (Boxes 1-12), but after that each year was treated separately.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Stanford Events.; Performing arts--California
Collection Contents
- Abramowitz, Jonathon - 3/8/74 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "Adams to Jefferson and Jefferson to Adams" - 4/20/76 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ailey, Alvin - Oct. 15-20, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Albee Directs Albee - 10/9/78 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Aman Folk Ballet - 1/16/76 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Aman Folk Ensemble - 11/30/73 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Amati Quartet - 4/25/75 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ameling, Elly - Nov. 15 and 19, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- American Brass Quintet - 10/7/73 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- American Brass Quintet - 4/17/77 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- American Film Theater Press - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Are You Now Or Have You Ever Been - 10/28/76 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ax, Emanuel - 2/28/75 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bach Aria Group - 2/18/77 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Ballad of Sacco and Vanzetti (canceled) - 2/6/72 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Barbosa, Carolos - Lima - 10/28/77 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Barocco, Secolo - 2/2/73 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Beaux Arts Trio - 11/5/74 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Beaux Arts Trio - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Bernstein, Seymour - 3/1/74 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bicentennial Fest. of Amer. Music - General Information - 4/3/76 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Blackett, Joy - 11/9/73 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Blackett, Joy - 1973-74 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Brico, Antonia - 2/10/75 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bloch, Boris - 1977-78 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- The Borodin Quartet - 4/29/73 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Ballet - March 14-16, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Chamber Music Society of Lincoln - Oct. 22, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Chaplin Film Series - 1973-74 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Chiligirian String Quartet - 11/4/77 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Chiligirian String Quartet - Nov. 7, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Chilkat Dancers - 2/24/73 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Ciccolini, Aldo - 1/22/78 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- City Center Acting Company - 4/17/75 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Cleveland Quartet - 10/16/73 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Cleveland Quartet - Feb. 3, 5, 7, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Concord Quartet - 5/5/73 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Contemporary Chamber Ensemble - 11/7/75 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Cronkite, Walter - 9/28/75 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Dale, Clamma - 10/13/78 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Dance Celebration - June 18, 19, 20, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Dance Films - 2/10/75 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Dance Programs - 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Dance Spectrum - 3/11 and 12/78 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Deseret String Band - 4/3/76 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- The Dillards - 9/1/74 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Driftwood, Jimmy - 7/3/76 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Early Music Consort of London - 4/26/74 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Early Music Consort of London - 4/9/76 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Early Music Quartet - 4/15-18/75 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Eliot Feld Ballet - 2/1-3/77 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- The Ensemble for Early Music - 11/5/76 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Entremont, Philippe - 10/14/77 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ferrer, Jose - 1/18/77 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fine Arts Quartet with Walter Trampler - 4/24-26/77 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- First Chamber Dance Company - 1/30-31/75 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Gillespie, Dizzy - 4/4/75 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Golabek, Mona - 4/19/74 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Goslar's Pantomime Circus - 1/16-20/73 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Graffman, Gary, pianist - 10/17/72 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 11/11/73 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 11/19,22,24/74 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 4/11,14,16/75 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 11/14,16,19/76 and 2/22,25,27/77 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 11/6,8,11/77 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 11/15,17,19/78 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Harkess Ballet - 11/11/72 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Harpsichord Series - 1972-73 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Hartford Ballet - 10/31/75 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Hartford, John - 9/15/74 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Herfitz, Daniel - 4/20/73 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Kipnis, Igor - Nov. 3, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- IL Divertimento - 11/14/78 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Louis Falco Dance Company - 4/10,11/75 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Martha Graham Dance - 11/15-27/74 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Midsummer Mozart - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Mummenschanz - 4/6/76 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Music From Marboro - 2/25/73 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Music From Marboro - 2/10/74 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Music From Marboro - 3/7/75 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Music From Marboro - 3/12/76 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Music From Marboro - 11/9/76 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Music From Marboro - 4/16/78 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- National Dance Company of Senegal -10/24,25/74 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Anthony Newman - 1/26/73 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Newyork Camerata - 5/19/73 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Newyork Chamber Soloists (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Newyork Chamber Soloists - 10/13,14/72 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Newyork Chamber Soloists - 10/8/74 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Newyork Pro Musica - 5/6.8.12/73 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Newyork String Sextet - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Newyork Woodwind Quintet - 2/24/78 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- "Oh Coward" - Declined - Summer, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- One-Man Shows - 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Chris Parkening - 1/25/74 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Peninsulairs Conference - Summer, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Murray Perahia, Pianist - 4/6/73 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Daniel Philips - YCA - 2/11/77 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Pilobolous Dance Theater - 2/5,6/76 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Eleo Pomare Dance Company - 2/5/75 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Posin Dance Company - Oct. 28, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 7/4-8/72 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - July, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 10/26/73 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 7/2-6/74 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 10/4/74 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 7/1,2,3,4/75 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 7/3/76 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 7/77 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 7/77 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Quadro Hotteterre - 3/3/78 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Rampal/Veyron-Lacroix - 2/8/74 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Red Detachment of Women - 1/5/73 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Franois Regnat, Piano - 5/7/76 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Repertory Dance Theater of Utah - 2/15-17/73 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- John Roberts (Box 9, Folder 5)
- The Romeros -10/18/74 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- St.Paul Chamber Orchestra - 1/20/78 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- San Francisco Symphony - 8/72 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- San Francisco Symphony - October 1, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- San Francisco Symphony - 1978-79 Season (Box 9, Folder 10)
- The Slovak Chamber Orchestra - Cancelled - 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Sour Cream - 10/14/75 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Speculum Musicae - 1/21/73 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- D. Stickney "A Lovely Light" - 1/12/73 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Elly Stone (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Jefferey Swann - YCA - 11/12/76 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Tashi - 1/21/75 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Belly Taylor Trio - Dec. 1. 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Paul Taylor Flyer and Mail Quote (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Paul Taylor Dance Company (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Paul Taylor Dance Company #2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Tel Aviv Quartet w/y. Ettlinger - 2/13/76 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Don Thomas, Cello - 11/12/75 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Marcus Thomson - YCA - 1/21/77 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- The Tokyo String Quartet - 2/14,16,18,/75 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- The Tokyo String Quartet - 10/22/78 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Le Treteau de Paris - 1961 through 1965 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Le Treteau de Paris - 4/7/73 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Le Treteau de Paris - Cancelled - 4/6/74 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Totentanz - 3/11,12/78 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Utah Repertory Dance Theatre - 4/6,7,8/77 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Valenti, Fernando - 4/13/73 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Valenti, Fernando, harpsichord - 2/20/76 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Virtuosi di Roma (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Walker, Theodore J. (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Waverly Consort - 2/22/74 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Dennis Wayne's Dancers - Jan. 26,27, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Webster, Michael - 11/8/74 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Williams, Emlyn - 11/14/72 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Windom, William, thurber - 2/15/74 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Paul Winter Consort - 4/23/76 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- The State of Man - 1/17/75 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- World of Gilbert and Sullivan - 11/1/74 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- World of Gilbert and Sullivan - 10/17-78/78 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Yajima, Hiroko, violin - 2/27/76 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Yepes, Narciso - 11/2/73 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Yepes, Narciso - 4/1/77 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Young Concert Series - 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Young Concer Series - 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Young Concert Artists Series - 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Zabaleta, Nicanor, harp - 1/30/76 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Zabaleta, Nicanor - 2/17/78 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Zerbe, Anthony (1979) (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Academy of St. Martin in the Fields - 4/21/79 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Adni, Daniel - March 13, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Aeolian Chamber Players - April 27, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Almeida, Laurindo - April 13, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Aman - 1/26/79 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Ameling, Elly - 10/26/79 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Bartok String Quartet - January 31, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Berlin Philharmonic Octet - 4/21/79 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Pablo Casals Trio - April 29, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Curtin, Phyllis - July 8-21, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Dermota, Anton - May 21, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Dichter, Misha and Cipa - 1/12/79 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Fialkowska, Janina - April 10, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Gillespie, Dizzy - March 16, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Greenwood Consort - April 29, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Guarneri String Quartet - 11/6,9,11/79 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Houle / Wibaux - Feb. 3, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Juilliard String Quartet - Feb. 10-11, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Kavhfian, Ida, and Edward Aver - 10/16/79 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Bella Lewitzky Dance Company - 10/19/79 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Lorimer, Michael - May 4, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Midsummer Mozart - 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Music From Marlboro - March 4, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- New England Conservatory Ragtime Ensemble - 10/12/79 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Parkening, Christopher - 1/23/79 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Pilobolus - March 1-3, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Pilobolus - March 1,2,3, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Pittsburg Symphony Chamber Orchestra - 1/20/79 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 6/29,30/79; 7/4/79 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Preservation Hall-Games, Prizes, Entertainment - 4 July 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Rejto, Peter, and Michelle Cooker - 10/16/79 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Symphony - 10/7/79 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Sour Cream - 10/28/79 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Starker, Janos - April 6, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Stoltzman, Richard - 10/23/79 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Suzuki - 10/6/79 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Tarr / Kent - 11/2/79 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Tuckwell, Barry - 11/13/79 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Vienna Chamber Players - March 9, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Walker / Johnson / Jackson - 2/23/79 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Zuckerman / Bonell - 2/16/79 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- The Acting Company - 1/25,26/80 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Akiyoshi / Tabackin - Feb. 2, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Alvin Ailey Dance Company - March 10, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Amadeus String Quartet - May 2, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- California Music Center - July 15, 22, 29, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Chilingirian String Quartet - April 18, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Cohen, Robert - 3/2/80 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Collard, Jean Philippe - Oct. 17, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Dee, Ruby, and Ossie Davis - April 25, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Feather, Leonard - 1/31/80 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Guarneri - 10/29,31/80, and 11/2/80 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Guarneri / Vermeer - Feb. 24, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Henry Holt Opera Lecture - Oct. 14, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Houle / Wibaux - 2/10 to 3/8, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Joffrey II - January 17 and 18, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Kalichstein, Laredo, Robinson Trio - Nov. 23, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Karr, Gary / Harmon Lewis - 2/8/80 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Kavafian, Ida - Nov. 14, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Moravec, Ivan - 2/15/80 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Music From Marlboro - 2/17/80 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- New York Chamber Soloist - January 8-11, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Ohyama, Heiichiro - 1/22/80 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Ohio Ballet - Oct. 23, 24, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Prague String Quartet - Oct. 19, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band, 4th of July Picnic, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - June 27, 28 and July 4, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Radford, Ronald - April 8, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Repertory Dance Theatre - Feb. 28, 29, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Rollins, Sonny - Feb. 22, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Rosen, Charles - July 7-18, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Rosen, Charles - April 11, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Rosen, Nathaniel - 4/13/80 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Samelson, Peter - Nov. 7, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- S.F. Symphony - July 18, 25, August 1, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Seeger, Pete / Odetta - 4/4/80 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Tashi - April 20, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Villella, Edward - 1/13/80 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Waverly Consort - 3/4/80 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Yepes, Narciso - Nov. 22, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Zabaleta, Nicanor - 2/1/80 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Adni, Daniel - July 15, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Avril, Franck (YCA) - November 11, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Beaux Arts Trio - April 15, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Bressler, Charles - Jan. 25, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Carroll, Pat - Jan. 30, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Chamber Music West - June 19, 24, 26, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Crow's Nest - April 1-3, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Emerson Quartet - April 22-24, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Feather, Leonard - 11/17, 1/26, and 4/13, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Funt, Allen - Only Human (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Guarneri Quartet - November 4, 6, 8, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Hoch, Beberly (Sung Ju Lee) - Feb. 11, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Holliger, Heinz - April 5, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Jazzantiqua- April 17, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- July 4, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Karr, Gary, and Harmon Lewis - Oct. 23, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Kavafian, Ida - July 22, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- LA 4 - November 21, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Lar Lubovitch Dance Co. - Jan. 21-23, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Licad, Cecile (Peter Serkin-cancelled) - May 1, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Music By Three (YCA) - October 30, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Music From Marlboro - Feb. 20, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Nikolais Dance Company - March 4-7, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Nutcracker - Dec. 3, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Odessa Balalaikas - Feb. 13, 14, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Paillard Chamber Orchestra - Jan. 16, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Panocha Quartet - Oct. 25, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Paratores, Anthony and Joseph - Feb. 27, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Perlman, Itzhak - March 13, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Pilobolus - Oct. 14, 15, 16, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - July 4, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- PHJB, Prizes - 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Serkin, Peter - May 1, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Shearing, George - Nov. 19, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Stoltzman, Trampler, Luvisi- November 10, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- String Trio - April 10, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Lew Tabackin Trio - Jan. 9, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Billy Taylor Trio - April 26, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Vermeer Quartet - Feb. 22, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Von Ramm, Andrea, Master Class - October 6, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Wilson, Ramson, and Nancy Allen - Feb. 6, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Zukerman, Pinchas - December 15, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Akiyoshi, Toshiko - January 22, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Akiyoshi, Toshiko - January 22, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Ax, Emanuel - November 7, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Bylsma, Anner - Nov. 5, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Calliope Renaissance Band - Feb. 28, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- The Chieftains - March 12, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Cosma, Sofia (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Davidovich, Bella - Oct. 15, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Edelmann, Sergei - January 10, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Emerson Quartet - April 14, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Empire Brass Quintet - Nov. 3, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Feather, Leonard - Nov. 16, 1981 and Jan. 18, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Guarneri String Quartet - November 14 and 17, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Juillet, Chantal - Feb. 10, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Juilliard Quartet - Jan. 29, 31, Feb. 3, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Kalichstein, Laredo, Robinson - Feb. 26, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Moe Koffman Jazz - Feb. 20, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Bella Lewitzky Dance Company - Oct. 20 and 22, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Limon, Jose - March 5, 6, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Midsummer Mozart - July 16, 23, 30 1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Music By 3 - Oct. 24, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Music From Marlboro - April 18, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Newport Jazz Festival All Stars - Oct. 30, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- New York Chamber Soloists - Jan. 6 and *, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Ohlsson, Garrick - May 5, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Orford Quartet - Dec. 1, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Pollack, Daniel - April 3, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - 5th of July, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Repertory Dance Theatre - Jan. 15, 16, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Starker, Janos - April 25, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Stoltzman / Douglas - April 9, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Wincenc, Carol, and Nathan Schwartz - April 16, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Zabaleta, Nicanor (Nancy Allen, replacement) - Feb. 7, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Bolling, Claude, with Herbie Mann - 10/16/83 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Bream, Julian - Nov. 7, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- California Bach Society, Brahm's Birthday - May 7, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center - Feb. 27, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- The Cleveland Quartet - Feb. 16, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Concord String Quartet - Oct. 26, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- The Emerson Quartet - Feb. 2, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Endellion Quartet - April 13, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Robin Flower Band - Feb. 1, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Philip Glass Ensemble - April 17, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Glickman, Sylvia - Jan. 25, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Guarneri String Quartet - Nov. 13 and 16, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Hollander, Loren - June 4, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Kalichstein-Laredo-Robinson Trio - Nov. 2, 4, 6, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Lorimer, Michael - March 12, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Maillet, Paul - Oct. 23, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Martin, Marya - Feb. 20, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- The McLain Family Band - April 2, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Midsummer Mozart - July 24, 31, August 7, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Musicians From Marlboro - March 30, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- A Musical Offering - Jan. 16, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- New England Ragtime Ensemble - April 23, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Oberlin Dance Collective - April 27 and 29, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Paillard Chamber Orchestra - Oct. 14, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Perahia, Murray - March 4, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Phillips, Peter - Oct. 3-9, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Pilobolus Dance Theatre - Nov. 30, Dec. 1, 2, 3, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Preservation Hall Jazz Band - July 4, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- P.D.Q. Bach - 10/31/83 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Schonberg, Harold - Jan. 26, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Shelton, Lucy - Jan. 28, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Sheynkman, Emanuil - Feb. 4, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Shumsky, Oscar - Jan. 7, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- The Suk Trio - April 10, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Tashi - Feb. 23, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- The Paul Taylor Dance Company - Jan. 19, 20 and 21, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Treger, Charles, and Andre Watts - April 24, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Ameling, Elly - April 15, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Angelou, Maya - 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Bartok Quartet - Feb. 5, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Bishop-Kovacevich, Steven - Feb. 12, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Bolling, Claude - Oct. 24, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Borodin Trio - 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Brey, Carter - Jan. 20, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Burns, Stephen - April 27, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Congressional Arts Conference - Nov. 10, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Emerson String Quartet - Feb. 22, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Emmanuel Wind Quartet - Nov. 18, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Empire Brass Quintet - Nov. 18, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Fitzwilliam String Quartet - April 4, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Fisk Organ Series - 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Gillespie, Dizzy - Aug. 4, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Martha Graham Dance Company - Oct. 1, 2 and 3, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Gregory, Dick - Oct. 16, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Guarneri String Quartet - Nov. 11 and 14, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- I Solisti di Zagreb - Feb. 8, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Margaret Jenkins Dance Company - May 3 and 4, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Philip Jones Brass Ensemble - April 8, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Kavafian, Ani - April 18, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- The King's Singers - March 10, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Kronos Quartet - May 2, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Licad, Cecile - April 29, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- McCorkle, Susannah - Feb. 4, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- McLain Family Band - July 4, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Midsummer Mozart - July 13, 20, 27, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Mime Musica - March 17, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Momix Dance Group - Oct. 18-20, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Music From Marlboro - Feb. 1, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- The Musicians of Swanne Alley - March 11, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Nanney, Herbert (Fisk) - May 6, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Near, Holly - Feb. 10, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Noehren, Robert - Oct. 14, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Paratore, Anthony and Joseph - Oct. 26, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Polish Jazz Band - May 10, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Prague String Quartet - Oct. 17, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Preston, Simon - July 1, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Ririe-Woodbury Dance Co. - Jan. 27, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Sarton, May - April 9, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Serkin, Peter - Jan. 13 and 15, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)